{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35acff124495add200a5"},"product_asin":"B01NB0YHKG","QAs":[{"question":"What kind of fragrance does it have?","answer":"Good fragrance","votes":"0","username":"MOHANRAM S.T.","date":"2021-09-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this face powder for all","answer":"Yes, except babies.","votes":"0","username":"Anony","date":"2020-06-16 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35adff124495add200a9"},"product_asin":"B00JJGW4M8","QAs":[{"question":"Kya face par use kar sakte hai","answer":"Yes why not, it is a talcum powder","votes":"0","username":"Vigish Kishon","date":"2022-03-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its shows 31 may 21, is it already expired","answer":"You may get new one, if order now","votes":"0","username":"Vigish Kishon","date":"2022-03-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Nivea Musk Talc old stock?","answer":"They deliver new/fresh products.","votes":"0","username":"Meghal Mody","date":"2022-01-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date","answer":"06/23","votes":"0","username":"MASS READYMADES…","date":"2022-01-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is expiry date","answer":"08/05/2022","votes":"0","username":"Suresh P A","date":"2021-10-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date elapsed.. best before shows 31May2021 and today is 30Aug2021.. andd it's not returnable. Why?","answer":"Product was Good.","votes":"0","username":"Dinesh S B","date":"2021-09-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"This product pure natural?","answer":"This is pure product.i use last five years and no issues regarding quality.","votes":"0","username":"Ranjit Kumar Agrawal","date":"2021-07-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"May i clearance about  the date of manufacture and expiry date month year","answer":"Quality is not good","votes":"0","username":"Sajitkhan S Malek","date":"2021-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"What will be mfg & exp date of product if i order today from primenow - hypercity malad","answer":"Good Product","votes":"0","username":"SUSHANT","date":"2021-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the expiry date","answer":"Expiry date- 2-2023","votes":"0","username":"The Pet HoUse","date":"2021-04-23 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35aeff124495add200b7"},"product_asin":"B07DJNX6JH","QAs":[{"question":"Expires on which date?","answer":"2021","votes":"0","username":"krishna","date":"2020-03-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can this be used on  Balls / Groin area","answer":"Yed","votes":"0","username":"Singh Brothers™","date":"2020-02-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it liquid or powder?","answer":"Powder","votes":"0","username":"Prem Dewangan","date":"2019-10-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this is original candid powder ?","answer":"Not sure bcz smells are not felling like before I used candid buy through market","votes":"0","username":"Rakesh Kumar","date":"2019-10-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it be used on scalp?","answer":"I think no.","votes":"0","username":"Rajesh Kumar","date":"2019-09-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Deliver charges?","answer":"No Delivery Charge","votes":"0","username":"Saurabh Chaudhary","date":"2019-10-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use it on my back","answer":"Yes you can use it","votes":"0","username":"Lakshmi Venkateshwara Distribu…","date":"2019-07-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"I didn't get 5 products ,i ordered on 20th june 2019. When i get my orders?","answer":"Please go for Cancel to all unreachad Product.I already facing same problem in flipkart.And no any currect answer in customer care excutive.Other vise Wait & Watch# Jai Shri Ram #see less","votes":"0","username":"Prem Dewangan","date":"2019-10-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"can it be used for baby","answer":"Not sure about that, probable not","votes":"0","username":"Gaurav","date":"2019-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"can it be used for under thigh","answer":"Its exactly for that pyrpose","votes":"0","username":"Gaurav","date":"2019-06-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35aeff124495add200c2"},"product_asin":"B0050QW3H2","QAs":[{"question":"What is difference between mask talc and pure talc?","answer":"Musk talc has very light Musk fragrance","votes":"0","username":"Gopal Pawar","date":"2022-09-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date?","answer":"Exactly 2 years. But remember it is talcum powder always safe.","votes":"0","username":"SASWATI","date":"2021-04-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"can i use this for pubg match?","answer":"(1) Please clarify ,about how you would like to use  this personal talc of the human body in the match .(2) It's OK for Carrom Board match .,to spray the talc on  the board for coins to move smoothely on the board.(3) If the customer can explain his need & proposed mode of use of this talc in his pubg match , I can really help him out .(4) I wait for the reply from this customer .see less","votes":"0","username":"DR.AS RAO","date":"2020-08-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the bottle refillable once empty?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Aman kumar","date":"2020-03-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this nivea talc contain mint...?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"ANIL","date":"2019-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use it on face?","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"Abhishek jha","date":"2016-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"What are the manufacturing and expiry dates of this product","answer":"mfg date is 07/2015and exp date is 06/2017 respectivaly.","votes":"0","username":"Hitendra kumar","date":"2016-01-26 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35aeff124495add200ca"},"product_asin":"B00N5K46NO","QAs":[{"question":"What is the expire date of the product","answer":"Use before 24 months from Pkd","votes":"0","username":"Raj Kumar Singh","date":"2019-08-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can it absorbs sweat","answer":"Yeah it helps absorb sweat, keeping the area free from body odour.","votes":"0","username":"Puranjay M","date":"2019-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"When you add this item to amazon prime?","answer":"Yes this item is amazon prime","votes":"0","username":"Raj Kumar Singh","date":"2019-08-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Add this to amazon prime.","answer":"Yes add this to amazon prime","votes":"0","username":"Raj Kumar Singh","date":"2019-08-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Delivery charges so high","answer":"Yes delivery charges to high","votes":"0","username":"Raj Kumar Singh","date":"2019-08-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it for men","answer":"Its for all","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2018-09-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"can i get two at a time ?","answer":"Not one at a time","votes":"0","username":"Raj Kumar Singh","date":"2019-08-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it for summers?","answer":"Yes it is summers","votes":"0","username":"Raj Kumar Singh","date":"2019-08-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the manufacturing and expiry date?","answer":"Packed Date: May 2017//Expiry: 24 months from packed date","votes":"0","username":"Shyamal Kr Chowdhury","date":"2017-12-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"can we use it for face?????","answer":"You can use a pretty light amount as it is not a face powder or else your face will look caky. Generous amount of this talc on face is completely okay:)","votes":"0","username":"Tanya","date":"2016-11-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35aeff124495add200d5"},"product_asin":"B07BDNBD5F","QAs":[{"question":"This product is available for bijapur .","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Mittal Medical Store®","date":"2019-11-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35aeff124495add200da"},"product_asin":"B00N5K47H4","QAs":[{"question":"Expiry date","answer":"Cinthol Talc is best before 24 months from the date of manufacturing.","votes":"0","username":"GODREJ CONSUMER PRODUCTS LTD","date":"2022-03-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can be cooled as much Navratna powder?","answer":"Cinthol Lime Talc keeps you feeling fresh and energized all day. It also provides protection from perspiration.","votes":"0","username":"Ashi J.","date":"2021-06-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"can i use it on face?","answer":"Yes but no so much only little","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2019-10-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date","answer":"No expiry date","votes":"0","username":"Ayush Garg","date":"2019-08-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is  spray","answer":"No, it is not a spray. It is talcum powder.","votes":"0","username":"Kash","date":"2019-04-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Women also use or not","answer":"Can be used by women.","votes":"0","username":"Usha Rao","date":"2018-03-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it smells the same like cinthol lemon fresh soap ? What abput the fragrance is it strong nd longlasting?  Its original product?","answer":"The fragrance is strong and longlasting.","votes":"0","username":"Kash","date":"2019-04-30 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35aeff124495add200e2"},"product_asin":"B01N3C4SYM","QAs":[{"question":"Gentleman or morning dew which one is better ?","answer":"About gentleman i don't know, but morning dew is awesome! I love it!","votes":"0","username":"gopal","date":"2022-09-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"will you deliver it to kolkata?","answer":"Yes we will deliver to any part of India.","votes":"0","username":"Shopgenx Ventures","date":"2022-09-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why does it contain the banned, cancer causing chemical - triclosan?","answer":"Smoothie and ever last freshness","votes":"0","username":"Dinesh K.","date":"2022-09-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Mujhe 1 hi quentity cheye lakin 5 quentity dikha raha hai","answer":"5 is the total quantity displaced in my inventory. You can order 1 pc","votes":"0","username":"HARI OM AGENCY.","date":"2022-04-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expirrd date powder","answer":"Expiry date is 10/2024","votes":"0","username":"HARI OM AGENCY.","date":"2022-01-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"why am I not allowed to buy Yardley talcum powder?","answer":"I have been buying it for years and love it!","votes":"0","username":"Uttara Devi","date":"2022-09-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have ordered this product on 28 july 2020 today is 20 august 2020 but up to now i will not get this product. What can i do?","answer":"Have patience,it will reach sooner or later.","votes":"0","username":"Susmita","date":"2020-08-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it Sweat control as well","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Hemalatha Bunyan","date":"2020-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"can this be used for kids of 10yr","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Swarnendu Singha","date":"2019-10-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is for oily skin","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Savita","date":"2019-10-19 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35aeff124495add200ed"},"product_asin":"B00CQ40O90","QAs":[{"question":"Can it be used as a body massage powder?","answer":"Good 👍","votes":"0","username":"Sakhibahmed","date":"2022-06-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its original rate is 280 how can you cheat?","answer":"Good","votes":"0","username":"Sakhibahmed","date":"2022-06-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date?","answer":"Last day of the best before month available on product page of Amazon is the expiery date","votes":"-1","username":"Tarun SinhaRay","date":"2020-10-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expired date not found","answer":"Search best before in concerned page of Amazon app","votes":"0","username":"Tarun SinhaRay","date":"2020-10-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is shipping cost????","answer":"To be mentioned at the time of billing before purchase. May be free or may be charged.","votes":"0","username":"Tarun SinhaRay","date":"2020-10-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pay on delever","answer":"Whether it is available or not is mentioned in concerned page of product.","votes":"0","username":"Tarun SinhaRay","date":"2020-10-31 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we apply to face","answer":"Better to avoid.","votes":"0","username":"S N Chatterjee","date":"2019-05-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing date of the product","answer":"goood","votes":"0","username":"suman","date":"2019-07-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expire date","answer":"Given on the bottom of the pack. Mine was 8/20 purchased about 4-5 months back","votes":"0","username":"S","date":"2019-03-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expire date","answer":"Best before date is expiery date. Chect product page","votes":"0","username":"Tarun SinhaRay","date":"2020-10-31 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35afff124495add200f8"},"product_asin":"B00CQ414LW","QAs":[{"question":"Expired  date","answer":"Duplicate ponds powder because no smooth,different colour damage .Money waste dont refund my money. give me a check .No converted money.i suggest original ponds powder purchase local shop.","votes":"0","username":"Tirumanadham venkatarao","date":"2022-09-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want to buy small packs of all fragrances is it possible?","answer":"Don't buy","votes":"0","username":"Tirumanadham venkatarao","date":"2022-09-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this non comedogenic","answer":"Expired powder or damage dont no my money no refund.","votes":"0","username":"Tirumanadham venkatarao","date":"2022-09-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why mint is added in this new and improved version.  It’s now a prickly heat powder.  I have an allergy to","answer":"No use no allergy","votes":"0","username":"Tirumanadham venkatarao","date":"2022-09-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Whats the expiry date","answer":"25/1/24","votes":"0","username":"M/S Ankit Enterprises","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why is cost of ponds 200gm pack more (210 rs) and 400 gm pack less (280 rs) ?","answer":"280","votes":"0","username":"Tirumanadham venkatarao","date":"2022-09-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date where","answer":"I see expire date long time powder damage.","votes":"0","username":"Tirumanadham venkatarao","date":"2022-09-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"This is talc less powder","answer":"No it is an excellent product.","votes":"0","username":"Ganeswar Majhi","date":"2021-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it contain sulphate or paraben or harmful chemicals ?","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"Ganeswar Majhi","date":"2021-06-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Ponds talc 400gm face wach free","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2021-05-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35afff124495add20103"},"product_asin":"B006LXD6C4","QAs":[{"question":"What is expiry date in prsent","answer":"Dear frnd, Cheating is Amazon's habbit, they supply this item after expiry date. Exp. Date is 02/21. By the way this brand of powder is my favourite and using it for long time.","votes":"0","username":"shubhakar dubey","date":"2021-08-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date of this product?","answer":"Fully used & emptied box a week ago. Pl","votes":"0","username":"Ravindranath","date":"2021-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we apply it on face also","answer":"I am using on Face also","votes":"0","username":"XYZ","date":"2021-03-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Mfd and expiry date","answer":"Thank you for choosing our product. The manufacturing date of Axe Signature Denim Cologne Talc is mentioned at the back of the pack and is best before 24 months from the date of packaging.","votes":"0","username":"Hindustan Unilever Limited.","date":"2020-08-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Its expiry date is somewhere in 2019?","answer":"No, it's July 2021","votes":"0","username":"K Parashar","date":"2020-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why have I received a damaged bottle the powder is coming out and someone had tampered the product very bad product ... refund the amount back","answer":"May be that particular bottle was damaged, ask for replacement.","votes":"0","username":"K Parashar","date":"2020-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"expiry date of this product?","answer":"Thank you for choosing our product. The expiry date of Axe Signature Denim Cologne Talc is 24 months from the date of packaging.","votes":"0","username":"Hindustan Unilever Limited.","date":"2020-07-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why to purchase two at a time? Is it old stock?","answer":"Users are more, so daily usage is extra.a","votes":"0","username":"K Parashar","date":"2020-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Mfd and Expiry date....","answer":"03/19","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2020-03-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Mfd and Expiry date","answer":"Thank you for choosing our product. The manufacture date of Axe Signature Denim Cologne Talc is mentioned at the back of the pack and it is best before 24 months from the date of packaging.","votes":"0","username":"Hindustan Unilever Limited.","date":"2020-07-02 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b0ff124495add20110"},"product_asin":"B00KENRWH2","QAs":[{"question":"What is the date of expiry date","answer":"10/23","votes":"0","username":"FAST2SHIP.","date":"2022-10-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which colour","answer":"Nice 🙂🙂🙂","votes":"0","username":"Durgadevi","date":"2022-01-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Call","answer":"Nice 🙂","votes":"0","username":"Durgadevi","date":"2022-01-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expire date?","answer":"Nice","votes":"0","username":"Durgadevi","date":"2022-01-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"The bottle in which talcum powder is kept is damaged.  Why l have been given  when the lid is punched.?","answer":"Powder bottle is damaged","votes":"0","username":"Ulfat","date":"2020-11-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"In this powder use from face?","answer":"No. it is for bad body odour. Its great for it.","votes":"0","username":"Zeba Rubaid","date":"2020-09-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is use for face powder?","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"Rao","date":"2020-09-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it chinese product ?","answer":"made in Malaysia.","votes":"1","username":"Anilkumar ks","date":"2020-06-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Which fragrances is better?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Vijay.Y","date":"2020-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is having delivery. Charge","answer":"Check the details on product page","votes":"1","username":"Placeholder","date":"2020-06-26 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b1ff124495add2011c"},"product_asin":"B00FX03IBK","QAs":[{"question":"This product is not show expiry","answer":"It is very smooth and gives a good fragrance good product","votes":"0","username":"santhi","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it made in india?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Ved Parkash Sharma","date":"2020-07-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have ordered 2 quantities which costs me 350?  I want to know that how many 300g box I'll receive for 350?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"tulsi","date":"2020-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many pack of this powder will i get ? 2 set means 4 packs ?","answer":"You will get 2. Buy one and get one free.","votes":"0","username":"Sunita Didwania","date":"2020-03-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"How many pack of this powder will i get ? 2 set means 4 packs ?","answer":"Yes,4packs","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2020-03-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Minumum 2 so recive total 4 ??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Gautam Lapsiya","date":"2020-03-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Wether it can apply on face?","answer":"Yes it can be applied on face.","votes":"0","username":"Atul Hemani","date":"2020-02-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Minimum quantity order is 2, and it is one plus one free that means 4×(300gm) ?","answer":"Yes, you will get 4 items.","votes":"0","username":"Gautam Lapsiya","date":"2019-11-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Quantity 2 means how many","answer":"TWO MEANS 2MUCH GOOD","votes":"-1","username":"Ved Parkash Sharma","date":"2019-10-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why it is compulsary to buy 2*2=4????","answer":"1*1=2 is the deal","votes":"0","username":"Dr Alin Jain","date":"2019-10-06 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b1ff124495add20127"},"product_asin":"B07G2QYWLP","QAs":[{"question":"Is this a Thailand product","answer":"No its very much an Indian product. Marketedand product of ITC.","votes":"0","username":"Yasmine Jalnawala","date":"2022-07-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use 8 month boy baby for this powder??","answer":"No. You can't use for small baby.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date","answer":"Expiry date products are not use","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why delivery charges of Rs 75  ?  It is total cheating the customers","answer":"Even I felt same. 75 for delivery is almost equivalent to the cost of the talc.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-02-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date of this product?","answer":"I do not think there is an expiry date to the talcum.","votes":"0","username":"Yasmine Jalnawala","date":"2021-12-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Hitesh kataria","date":"2022-07-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"I hear that shower to shower powder causes ovarian cancer, is this the same one that is from johnson & johnson which is banned in us ?","answer":"No. This Shower to Shower is not made by Johnson and Johnson","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"What are the expiry date and the manufacture date? Please mention the up to date info of these dates on the product info","answer":"We have to see the manufacturing date and expiry date","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"What are the ingredients in this product?","answer":"Pudina, dugdhapasni, jasadBhasm, starch, Zealand Mays, fragrance/odoriferous substance,salicylic Acid....etc","votes":"0","username":"John V.","date":"2021-04-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"I can use this powder for 1year baby boy","answer":"Yes you can. But conventionally we prefer Johnson Baby powder for babys as it is milder.","votes":"0","username":"Sudipta Chatterjee","date":"2020-04-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b1ff124495add20134"},"product_asin":"B008KH3VUG","QAs":[{"question":"How may powdet bottle and how many soap and its weight?","answer":"Dear valued consumer  Dermicool Prickly Heat Powder, Menthol - 150g Each (Pack Of 2), 150 g contains 2 Bottles of 150g each along with 2 Dettol soaps of 125g each.","votes":"0","username":"Reckitt Consumer Care","date":"2022-06-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much expirey date","answer":"36 month","votes":"0","username":"SONI DISTRIBUTOR JPR","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Both the bottles of 150g each.. or 75*2","answer":"EACH 150GM","votes":"0","username":"SONI DISTRIBUTOR JPR","date":"2022-05-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"v can use for baby","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"rasvinder s.","date":"2017-02-19 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b1ff124495add2013b"},"product_asin":"B00FQH5H6O","QAs":[{"question":"What is manufacturing and expiry date","answer":"2022 mfd and approximately 18months expired date","votes":"0","username":"GAURANGBHAI REVALIYA","date":"2022-07-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we apply it in face.","answer":"Don't exactly...its body lotion","votes":"0","username":"Romesh Kesharwani","date":"2021-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the manufacturing Date ?","answer":"05/2020","votes":"0","username":"Chandu jk","date":"2021-05-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's expiry date of this product?","answer":"EXPIRY DATE:-DECEMBER,2022","votes":"0","username":"Yusuf Enterprise","date":"2021-02-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"The quantity is less when i compared to my local shop, i have the snapshot to compare","answer":"Please report and return it if you aresure with evidence.","votes":"0","username":"Dr. ASHWANI KUMAR VERMA","date":"2021-06-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date of current product","answer":"expiry will be 2years from date of mfg.","votes":"0","username":"ANUGRAH AGRAWAL","date":"2021-03-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date","answer":"2022","votes":"0","username":"shreeji trading company","date":"2020-08-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is mfd and expiry date","answer":"Mfd 02/2020 U.B./01/2022","votes":"0","username":"DWIPANKAR Sethy","date":"2020-08-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this preckli heat","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Karuna","date":"2020-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it alcohol free?","answer":"YES It is alcohol free","votes":"0","username":"KAMAL AGRAWAL","date":"2020-01-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b1ff124495add20147"},"product_asin":"B091PWH27F","QAs":[{"question":"Is it good for face","answer":"Hello,","votes":"0","username":"Beautisoul","date":"2021-09-22 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b2ff124495add2014d"},"product_asin":"B091N6KRVY","QAs":[{"question":"What is the expiry of the product ?","answer":"Hey","votes":"0","username":"Beautisoul","date":"2021-10-22 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b2ff124495add20150"},"product_asin":"B00YXYZWQ6","QAs":[{"question":"this is pack of 2 i.e. we get 800 grams? right?","answer":"I have not weighed the contents but I think these are 400 gms packs . I have no doubt.","votes":"0","username":"PKB","date":"2022-09-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"i get only 1 instead of 2","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amz cust","date":"2022-09-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"It was ordered buy one get one but came Only one i rejected the order","answer":"Yes. Reject if you get one when buy 1 get1 free is written in description","votes":"0","username":"Amz cust","date":"2022-09-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it buy one get one...  but received only one why?","answer":"Check if buy 1 get 1 free in description","votes":"0","username":"Amz cust","date":"2022-09-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it pack of 2 or only 1?","answer":"Yes it is pack of 2 and good quality","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2020-11-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why there is only one 400 gm when its says buy one get one free?","answer":"Check if buy1 get 1 free written","votes":"0","username":"Amz cust","date":"2022-09-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will i be receiving 2 pieces of 400gm each or only 1 piece. i know that normally this product comes in a pack of 2 (buy 1 get 1) bt juz wanna b sure","answer":"You are eligible to receive 2pieces of 400 gram each. If you are not receiving then write review on their website that you didn't received the quantity as per their advertisement.","votes":"0","username":"Parth Patel","date":"2020-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it pack of 2 400*2","answer":"This is pack of two..... Buy one get one free... I really love this frangrance","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2020-05-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it pack of 2?","answer":"Yes it's pack of 2","votes":"0","username":"Pushparaj Krishnan","date":"2020-05-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Both are in 400gms","answer":"YES","votes":"0","username":"CHANDER Dua","date":"2020-02-19 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b3ff124495add2015b"},"product_asin":"B08WRR7VTQ","QAs":[{"question":"Date of Expiry","answer":"it will be written on case if it have","votes":"0","username":"Suresh N.","date":"2021-12-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this just 50gm or 150gm+50gm? The product details mentions the weight as 50gm","answer":"150+50","votes":"0","username":"Suresh N.","date":"2021-12-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please Tell  this product expiry date?","answer":"A personal advice, AMAZON has kept up to its reputation so Nothing to worry. The product is valid for more than a year.","votes":"0","username":"Noel","date":"2021-06-11 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b3ff124495add20162"},"product_asin":"B002ZVK88G","QAs":[{"question":"is this product for armpits?","answer":"Don't buy this product worst powder I have ever used.","votes":"0","username":"Anirban Banerjee…","date":"2022-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any delivery  fees","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Raju Trader","date":"2021-09-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it contain real chandan powder?","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"Rupesh","date":"2021-07-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Validity period this product","answer":"3 YEARS","votes":"0","username":"Rupesh","date":"2021-03-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Valid date from and to date?","answer":"FROM NOVEMBER 2020 TO NOVEMBER 2023","votes":"0","username":"Rupesh","date":"2021-03-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Net wt 300gm per peace","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Ajay Jain","date":"2021-02-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is expiry date, if i will purchase in November 2020","answer":"It will be depending on the seller from which dated stock he deliver, Normally Shelf life will be 2 years from the date of manufacturing.","votes":"0","username":"SARAN KUMAR","date":"2020-11-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use for face?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Dr Ashok Kaushal","date":"2020-08-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the net weight pack of single unit?","answer":"300 gram.","votes":"0","username":"Kalyansinghlodhi","date":"2020-08-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is net weight pack of single?","answer":"300gm","votes":"0","username":"Trogon Cookware","date":"2020-07-30 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b3ff124495add2016d"},"product_asin":"B00UYGK1FY","QAs":[{"question":"Are the 2 150gm each ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Charanjit kaur","date":"2019-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this good for kids or toddler?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Charanjit kaur","date":"2019-06-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b3ff124495add20170"},"product_asin":"B08YKC89XD","QAs":[{"question":"Can i used this powder for 1 year baby","answer":"PLS CONSULT YOUR PEDIATRICIAN FOR THIS","votes":"0","username":"ALP GLOBAL","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pls send expire date","answer":"Don't go not worthable not getting solved","votes":"0","username":"sireesh","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date kitni hai","answer":"MARCH 2025","votes":"0","username":"ALP GLOBAL","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is baby friendly or not ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"PM","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date??","answer":"MARCH 2025","votes":"0","username":"ALP GLOBAL","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it dusting powder?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Mona Lisa","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can be used for 3 year old child?","answer":"YES","votes":"0","username":"ALP GLOBAL","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing date?","answer":"1/1/2022","votes":"0","username":"Gurvinder singh","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the manufacturing and expire date of this product","answer":"Buy it to know","votes":"0","username":"AvidBuyer","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date?","answer":"Check on tin","votes":"0","username":"Mona Lisa","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b4ff124495add2017c"},"product_asin":"B09WDB671J","QAs":[{"question":"Can it be applied on face","answer":"No, you feel too much cool on your face. Better you can use on your body.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-06-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b4ff124495add2017e"},"product_asin":"B00YXZ1B4W","QAs":[{"question":"Boro plus ice prickly heat is baby powder?","answer":"No, Never use it on Babies. I use it for my armpits and it keeps me fresh for long time. I use it as deodorant. Very Good for Adults.","votes":"0","username":"AVI","date":"2019-08-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Would you recommend this for heat rash ?","answer":"Yes. It is very good. Soothing to the skin .","votes":"0","username":"anand sharma","date":"2019-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the MRP rate listed on the product?","answer":"100","votes":"-1","username":"PINTU KUMAR","date":"2019-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is cold or hot? I want cold powder for summer ?","answer":"Obviously it's cold...","votes":"-1","username":"Tuhin","date":"2019-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it best for summer?","answer":"Yeah sure...  It's really good to use in summer","votes":"0","username":"Tuhin","date":"2019-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Rs. 265 for how many?","answer":"It's price ₹100.. in 265 you get 2","votes":"1","username":"Tuhin","date":"2019-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Boro plus can use for 4 year old girl","answer":"Yes","votes":"-1","username":"gomathivanan","date":"2018-04-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the quoted price for one piece or more?","answer":"One piece","votes":"-1","username":"Tuhin","date":"2019-06-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"is it apply on face","answer":"No cause it has sensetional effect","votes":"0","username":"Taslim","date":"2017-02-10 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b6ff124495add2018e"},"product_asin":"B01412WVSG","QAs":[{"question":"Can we apply on face?","answer":"Yes.","votes":"0","username":"Pushpa Bane","date":"2022-03-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Navaratan cool powder 400 gm how much money","answer":"210","votes":"0","username":"Rohit Kumar Gupta…","date":"2021-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiredate","answer":"210","votes":"0","username":"Rohit Kumar Gupta…","date":"2021-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is there any option of return incase of damage product received.","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Rohit Kumar Gupta…","date":"2021-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"Return or replace avaibe?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Rohit Kumar Gupta…","date":"2021-05-10 00:00:00"},{"question":"400gm is true","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"BHAVANA","date":"2019-06-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why there is a lot of delivery chrge??","answer":"You have ordered at least ₹499/- worth of goods.  Delivery charge will be free.","votes":"0","username":"Rahul Agrawal","date":"2022-03-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"expire date of this product?","answer":"18 months","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2017-05-26 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b6ff124495add20197"},"product_asin":"B00DRE06NM","QAs":[{"question":"Expiry date of product","answer":"Very clearly mentioned on the side of the can. It's normally 3 years from date of mfg.","votes":"0","username":"Balasubramaniam R Iyer","date":"2022-05-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expired date?","answer":"mid 2024","votes":"0","username":"SUPERDEALS2","date":"2022-04-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we apply it on face","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Vijoy Kumar Prasad","date":"2021-10-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it free from harmful chemicals like sulphate or paraben?","answer":"These are not mentioned in the ingredients but it has triclosan which is a questionable chemical if you check it over the web.","votes":"0","username":"Zenith","date":"2021-05-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"is this product cruelty free","answer":"Good powder","votes":"0","username":"Henry Paul vas","date":"2020-10-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"I need yardley lavender talcum powder not london morning dew how can i select lavender","answer":"By amazon","votes":"0","username":"Henry Paul vas","date":"2020-10-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this a combo pack with two fragnances ?","answer":"250 gram One PCS","votes":"0","username":"Noushad.Calicut","date":"2020-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"long lasting smell or not","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2020-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Have its long lasting smell","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2020-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Imported from England?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Nahas b","date":"2020-03-19 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b6ff124495add201a2"},"product_asin":"B00CRDO2GQ","QAs":[{"question":"Is this is suitable for kids","answer":"yes","votes":"0","username":"RAMAN\"S","date":"2020-10-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Going to have this product. Please mention the manufacturing & expiry date","answer":"Appreciate your interest. The manufacturing date of Pond's Sandal Radiance Talcum Powder, Natural Sunscreen is mentioned on the base of the product and is best before 24 months from the date of packaging.","votes":"0","username":"Hindustan Unilever Limited.","date":"2020-08-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is manufacturing date","answer":"6/19","votes":"0","username":"CHUDAMANI BILHOR","date":"2020-07-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"to use it as a sunscreen......what is the applying process??","answer":"This can be used like other talcum powder.","votes":"0","username":"Sethumadhavan Nair","date":"2019-06-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have very oily skin.....can I use this as a sunscreen???","answer":"no","votes":"0","username":"Vishal","date":"2019-06-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"does it really work as sunscreen????","answer":"Yea good","votes":"0","username":"Biju","date":"2019-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing and expiry date ??","answer":"It’s before expiry date","votes":"0","username":"Ravinder Pal singh","date":"2019-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is expire date","answer":"2 years from the manufacturer date","votes":"0","username":"Biju","date":"2019-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much mrp price of this product.i see rs.210 in retail shop.","answer":"240","votes":"0","username":"Biju","date":"2019-06-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it a Face Powder or not?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Biju","date":"2019-06-19 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b6ff124495add201ad"},"product_asin":"B06X3QZPJX","QAs":[{"question":"Expiry date?","answer":"27 nov 2022","votes":"0","username":"ADHIK","date":"2022-09-30 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it contain talc","answer":"Yes & it is cool n redreshing","votes":"0","username":"Unmesh A Londhe","date":"2022-08-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Please delivery charge free","answer":"40 rupees","votes":"0","username":"ADHIK","date":"2022-07-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use this talc for kids","answer":"Feel is very cool, so use in less amount, I suggest","votes":"0","username":"Unmesh A Londhe","date":"2022-07-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"When is the expiry?","answer":"consumption within 3 years so if ur mfg is 22 the exp is 25","votes":"0","username":"Ranju","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is expiry date?","answer":"3 years from the date of mfg so if mfg is 22 expirey is 25","votes":"0","username":"Ranju","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the Present mfg date and expiry date of this product??","answer":"2022 mfg exp 2025","votes":"0","username":"Ranju","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date ?","answer":"Normally it is 3 years","votes":"0","username":"Unmesh A Londhe","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"If i get expired so what i do","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Unmesh A Londhe","date":"2022-06-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date please","answer":"2025","votes":"0","username":"Ranju","date":"2022-06-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b6ff124495add201b8"},"product_asin":"B003GSPFFI","QAs":[{"question":"Is this product vegan and cruelty-free?","answer":"I hope so","votes":"0","username":"BABUKUMAR","date":"2022-05-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's talc  powder  colour","answer":"Colour is off white or light brown...not pure white","votes":"0","username":"Kindle Customer","date":"2021-11-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's this talcum powder colour","answer":"BABY PINK","votes":"0","username":"1 Place Beauty Stores","date":"2021-12-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"When did it expired? How many months it best before?","answer":"2years","votes":"0","username":"Alisha","date":"2021-11-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it safe to use for face?","answer":"I have been using it  since  3 to 4 months now, it didn't gave any rashes or anything. So u can definitely use it on ur face.","votes":"0","username":"Deepthi","date":"2021-08-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"is there only one bottle in price of 230?","answer":"I got on offer","votes":"0","username":"Alisha","date":"2021-11-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why is the picture wrong in the description? Is it actually biotique powder??","answer":"This picture is not related to the said Powder at all.","votes":"0","username":"T.PRASANNA KUMAR","date":"2021-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the complete list of ingredients along with its percentage?","answer":"neem5%, manjishtha root2%, makka seed 2%, yashad bhasm 1.5%, conch powder 1%, white sandalwood oil 1%, tulsi plant 1.5%","votes":"0","username":"1PLACE HEALTH FOODS","date":"2021-03-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we apply this powder for face?","answer":"Yes you can","votes":"0","username":"Alisha","date":"2020-12-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"You are saying it is talc free. But ingredients shows the talc in it??","answer":"There is a mild talc. Best powder for any type of skin","votes":"0","username":"najnin khatun","date":"2020-08-16 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b7ff124495add201c8"},"product_asin":"B00G4UCAD0","QAs":[{"question":"Talc is known to cause cancer. Is it true","answer":"I don't think so ,i use this product since more than 10 years and I am perfect.","votes":"0","username":"BHARAT KUMAR JAIN.","date":"2022-08-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use for face?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Vijoy Kumar Prasad","date":"2021-11-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"How can i use this powder","answer":"Direct body","votes":"0","username":"aman","date":"2021-11-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"How I want 2 yadkey talc powder gold","answer":"Please you can purchase.","votes":"0","username":"BEAUTY_SOLUTION","date":"2021-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"This is fongal inspection Powder?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"aman","date":"2021-11-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"How is the smell of the Powder","answer":"Its letrally amazing smell. Everyone have to try at once . I m dam sure the yardley London will never disappointed You!....","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2021-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use as summer cooling powder?","answer":"No it's not a cooling talc","votes":"0","username":"Prudhvi","date":"2021-04-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the material of the talcum box? Is it plastic? or is it metal?","answer":"Very very cheap quality.","votes":"0","username":"vicky j.","date":"2021-04-15 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does it have magnesium asbestos ??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2021-04-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it returnable","answer":"Non returnable item.","votes":"0","username":"Anmol","date":"2021-04-15 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b7ff124495add201d3"},"product_asin":"B00N5K48R8","QAs":[{"question":"Which colour bottle is good smelling?","answer":"I have tried only blue and its very nice smell","votes":"0","username":"Amazon_Customer DN","date":"2022-07-11 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is its expiry date ?? Please tell me. 🙏🙏","answer":"Excellent Product by Godrej as always. Kindly use within 24 months from it,s packing date which is mentioned on it","votes":"0","username":"RACHIT KUMAR","date":"2022-04-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date?","answer":"Cinthol Talc is best before 24 months from the date of manufacturing.","votes":"0","username":"GODREJ CONSUMER PRODUCTS LTD","date":"2022-04-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date of this product?","answer":"Cinthol Talc is best before 24 months from the date of manufacturing.","votes":"0","username":"GODREJ CONSUMER PRODUCTS LTD","date":"2022-04-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much time i am wait","answer":"I is written on delivery time !","votes":"0","username":"Prem","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"What happen my parcel when come","answer":"You have to wait since it arrive to you !","votes":"0","username":"Prem","date":"2022-04-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use on face","answer":"Yes, you can use Cinthol Cool Talc on face.","votes":"0","username":"Ashi J.","date":"2021-07-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can v use for kids?","answer":"Yes, Cinthol Talc can be used by kids.","votes":"0","username":"Ashi J.","date":"2021-07-01 00:00:00"},{"question":"It for hitches","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"BHASKER","date":"2021-05-23 00:00:00"},{"question":"Why is amazon not selling this in fresh/pantry section ? why should i pay a delivery charge of 85-100 for this from other sellers way above mrp ?","answer":"Buy from corner store.","votes":"0","username":"BHASKER","date":"2021-05-23 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b7ff124495add201df"},"product_asin":"B09JWWJVDZ","QAs":[{"question":"It is works for ringworms ?.","answer":"Not.... But iching kaam ho jaya ge","votes":"0","username":"megha kapoor","date":"2022-10-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use it for under arms?","answer":"Yes u can use it","votes":"0","username":"saurabh singh","date":"2022-09-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Kya face me use kar sakte h","answer":"Avoid it on face … As it is very strong","votes":"0","username":"Divyansh Gupta","date":"2022-08-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Will it give smell to other people in home when you have used it?","answer":"No absolutely not","votes":"0","username":"saurabh singh","date":"2022-08-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Mens ya women","answer":"Both can use without any problem","votes":"0","username":"Unmesh A Londhe","date":"2022-08-21 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can i use it for dog?","answer":"Probably yes but consult vet before once","votes":"0","username":"Unmesh A Londhe","date":"2022-07-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can we use it for kids?","answer":"Yes, i am using it for my 4 months old. Helps cure rashes too.","votes":"0","username":"Ishrat","date":"2022-06-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date ?","answer":"2 years","votes":"0","username":"megha kapoor","date":"2022-06-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it safe for normal skin?","answer":"Yes it is","votes":"0","username":"megha kapoor","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have ordered 3 pack of 3 closip dusting powder but I received only 1 pack of 3.","answer":"Check to your order and complain to Amazon for your order","votes":"0","username":"megha kapoor","date":"2022-05-25 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b9ff124495add201ed"},"product_asin":"B00I4S8A6Q","QAs":[{"question":"Nicil cool powder can use 1 year baby","answer":"Better use baby powder n not this one","votes":"0","username":"balki","date":"2020-04-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"How much pcs in this","answer":"1","votes":"0","username":"Sachin","date":"2017-04-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"can this powder be applied to face","answer":"yes..can be applied for face also..","votes":"0","username":"balki","date":"2016-04-28 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35b9ff124495add201f1"},"product_asin":"B09B9K4RW6","QAs":[{"question":"Does it work for Fungal infection","answer":"yes it works ..","votes":"0","username":"Neha Grover","date":"2022-09-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"are these original or some generic","answer":"Original","votes":"0","username":"Abdul Bari Shaikh","date":"2022-07-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"What's it's expiry date?","answer":"It will be mentioned on the packaging.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2022-07-09 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35bbff124495add201f8"},"product_asin":"B077KB116K","QAs":[{"question":"What is the expiry date","answer":"I NEEDED A BIG ONE BUT I RECEIVED THREE OF THEM! IT IS VERY INCONVENIENT TO USE MANY THINGS! SO HOW CAN I TRY TO BUY MORE THINGS FROM YOU?","votes":"0","username":"MANCHI SARAT BABU","date":"2019-07-01 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35bbff124495add201fc"},"product_asin":"B01CNRSA3Q","QAs":[{"question":"Why heading line indicate 400gm quantity in this product??But in real box quantity show 100gm in this product","answer":"It is excellent!","votes":"0","username":"MANCHI SARAT BABU","date":"2020-11-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does navratan talc contain asbestos?","answer":"Not at all its pure","votes":"0","username":"Ayush Garg","date":"2019-08-17 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35bcff124495add20207"},"product_asin":"B091N5XQ88","QAs":[{"question":"Long lasting??","answer":"The Fragrance is long-lasting.This Cherry Blossom Perfumed Talcum has amazing fragrance of Sakura flowers.Its Top Note consists of Cherry, Peach and GrapefruitHeart Note consists of Cherry Blossom, Lily, Jasmine, and HaychintBase Note consists of White musk and Amber.see less","votes":"0","username":"Beautisoul","date":"2021-06-29 00:00:00"},{"question":"expire date ?","answer":"Hey","votes":"0","username":"Beautisoul","date":"2021-05-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this suitable for all skin type?","answer":"Yes. It is suitable for all skin types!","votes":"0","username":"Beautisoul","date":"2021-05-14 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35bdff124495add2020c"},"product_asin":"B08YKGP8WF","QAs":[{"question":"Can i used this powder for 1 year baby","answer":"PLS CONSULT YOUR PEDIATRICIAN FOR THIS","votes":"0","username":"ALP GLOBAL","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pls send expire date","answer":"Don't go not worthable not getting solved","votes":"0","username":"sireesh","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date kitni hai","answer":"MARCH 2025","votes":"0","username":"ALP GLOBAL","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is baby friendly or not ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"PM","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date??","answer":"MARCH 2025","votes":"0","username":"ALP GLOBAL","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it dusting powder?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Mona Lisa","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can be used for 3 year old child?","answer":"YES","votes":"0","username":"ALP GLOBAL","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing date?","answer":"1/1/2022","votes":"0","username":"Gurvinder singh","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the manufacturing and expire date of this product","answer":"Buy it to know","votes":"0","username":"AvidBuyer","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date?","answer":"Check on tin","votes":"0","username":"Mona Lisa","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35beff124495add2021a"},"product_asin":"B09VGSLZSY","QAs":[{"question":"What is the expiry date?","answer":"March 2025","votes":"0","username":"Vedi","date":"2022-05-30 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35beff124495add2021c"},"product_asin":"B07NJVMYZQ","QAs":[{"question":"Expiry date durmi cool powder","answer":"Dear Valued Consumer the Expire date of the Dermicool Dermicool Prickly Heat Powder, Menthol - 150g Each (Pack Of 3), 150 g is 2 years from the date of MFG.","votes":"0","username":"Reckitt Consumer Care","date":"2022-07-21 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35bfff124495add20222"},"product_asin":"B00MUKR09M","QAs":[{"question":"Can we use this on face","answer":"Never tried on face , but good for the body … soft smell","votes":"0","username":"Malini","date":"2022-05-07 00:00:00"},{"question":"which country maid it","answer":"Made for WIPRO UNZA in malaysia.","votes":"0","username":"AVINASH M.","date":"2021-01-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date ?","answer":"1/2023. 36 months from manufacturing day.","votes":"0","username":"Madhuvanti Arun Kalelkar","date":"2020-10-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"When is the expire date of this product","answer":"No expiry date was given. Had only written MFD see below and to use within 36 months of MFD date. It is all written in Chinese. Don't buy, the powder cap would come off with all powder at once. Waste product. Hope this helps...","votes":"0","username":"Shary","date":"2020-01-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Enchanteur powder manufacture place","answer":"Not sure!!","votes":"0","username":"Shary","date":"2019-12-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"expiry date of this product?","answer":"Dc 2021","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2019-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"It's too much delivery charges","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2019-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"How i buy it","answer":"In Amazon enter the product name and get it. You would get all most everything in Amazon....","votes":"0","username":"Shary","date":"2020-01-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"If we want to buy 12 there is any delivery charges?","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2019-06-09 00:00:00"},{"question":"is this original?","answer":"Yes 100% original","votes":"0","username":"NOVELTY STORES 0291","date":"2016-07-23 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35c0ff124495add2022f"},"product_asin":"B082JN1FZC","QAs":[{"question":"How much weight of this product? Receive only 400gm","answer":"In this image it is showing as 400 gm. If you are looking for the offer then it is 400 + 400 gm. But the offer has to be explicitly mentioned in the product page","votes":"0","username":"Biswa","date":"2022-10-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"There is combo pack or single","answer":"The product description on app says Pack of 2. But only one is delivered.","votes":"0","username":"Sid","date":"2022-09-27 00:00:00"},{"question":"pack of 2 ka matlab hai","answer":"This means 2 pieces in one pack.","votes":"0","username":"Raghava C.","date":"2022-09-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Have received only  one  piece though its stated buy 1 get 1 free. Completely misleading","answer":"Good","votes":"0","username":"Mohammad Rafiuddin","date":"2022-09-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"ordered as  buy one get 1 free but received only1 400 gram.please clarify?","answer":"Good","votes":"0","username":"Mohammad Rafiuddin","date":"2022-09-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it pack of 1 or pack of 2*400 gm?","answer":"Yes pack of 1. A single 400g unit","votes":"0","username":"Placeholder","date":"2022-08-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it a 400 gram or something else","answer":"400 GM and seems to be original from the fragrance. I trust Amazon and it's customer centric approach.","votes":"0","username":"Biswa","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"It was buy 1 get 1 but i got only 1. When called customer care, executive denied and said cant return and its not buy 1 get 1 offer","answer":"For me it was written Buy 1 and Get 1. 2nd time only 1 was delivered though it was written buy 1 and get 1. So I call customer care and refund was issued for 1.","votes":"0","username":"Biswa","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"Buy one get one offer now available or not","answer":"You need to check. If it is written and you have placed it then Amazon executive accept the mistake. But if it is not written then you should not assume and buy.","votes":"0","username":"Biswa","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"I have purchased buy one get one free scheme but i received only 1 piece. Either send me another piece or return it back.","answer":"Check the order which you have placed and see what is written there. Accordingly call cc and they will help for sure.","votes":"0","username":"Biswa","date":"2022-07-25 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35c1ff124495add2023d"},"product_asin":"B008KH3W3C","QAs":[{"question":"Is this powder is used for face or not","answer":"Not for face.","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2019-06-13 00:00:00"},{"question":"what is the expairy date","answer":"April 2017","votes":"0","username":"Gaurav N.","date":"2016-03-01 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35c2ff124495add20243"},"product_asin":"B00546YWD6","QAs":[{"question":"Can i used on infant","answer":"No don't use it infants.","votes":"0","username":"SASANK SHEKHAR TRIPATHY","date":"2021-10-08 00:00:00"},{"question":"4pack of 200-200 gms??","answer":"No,","votes":"0","username":"BEVERLY HILLS SALES PRIVATE LI…","date":"2021-04-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35c2ff124495add20249"},"product_asin":"B00DRE2ZNG","QAs":[{"question":"Is this price for one or two ?","answer":"Justf 1 of 300g","votes":"0","username":"Chandru","date":"2021-06-14 00:00:00"},{"question":"Date of expiry","answer":"Normally talcum powers do not have any expiry.","votes":"0","username":"Anandakrishnan","date":"2021-03-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it better than Biotique bio basil powder","answer":"I never used Biotique bio basil powder but I regularly use Gokul Santol since 1992 although it lost its quality for time when packing was changed and now again as it was in 90s.","votes":"0","username":"Aravinda Atluri","date":"2020-07-26 00:00:00"},{"question":"Powder color is white or sandal?","answer":"Ivory that's litter colour of sandal but not write it smells really good","votes":"0","username":"Savinay Sharma","date":"2020-07-17 00:00:00"},{"question":"it's MRP?","answer":"Rs. 180.00 for 300g  per unit","votes":"0","username":"M. R. Sankarnarayanan","date":"2020-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"I want more pack of mysore sandal soaps along with this pack and santoor soaps pack Can you send them on free delivery.","answer":"Its up your wish","votes":"0","username":"M. R. Sankarnarayanan","date":"2020-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Dod we want to give money for delivery boy","answer":"No, not necessary","votes":"0","username":"M. R. Sankarnarayanan","date":"2020-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Dod we want to give money for delivery boy","answer":"No","votes":"0","username":"M. R. Sankarnarayanan","date":"2020-07-16 00:00:00"},{"question":"Anyone who has bought the product, could you please post a pic of the ingredients mentioned on the back.","answer":"Unable to attach photos. I have posted a revised review with photos","votes":"0","username":"Santa","date":"2019-02-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"Use of gokul sandal","answer":"good smell , my family like this item above 20 years.","votes":"0","username":"Raghavaiah","date":"2018-12-29 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35c2ff124495add20254"},"product_asin":"B07CB6SSJZ","QAs":[{"question":"Each pack 150gm?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Amazon Customer","date":"2019-10-07 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35c3ff124495add20256"},"product_asin":"B08Z33GN88","QAs":[{"question":"What is expiry date for this product?","answer":"08/2023","votes":"0","username":"SS","date":"2022-04-12 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is the product original??","answer":"ABSOLUTELY","votes":"0","username":"Navneet","date":"2021-07-30 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35c3ff124495add20259"},"product_asin":"B08YKJ4HJH","QAs":[{"question":"Can i used this powder for 1 year baby","answer":"PLS CONSULT YOUR PEDIATRICIAN FOR THIS","votes":"0","username":"ALP GLOBAL","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Pls send expire date","answer":"Don't go not worthable not getting solved","votes":"0","username":"sireesh","date":"2022-05-19 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date kitni hai","answer":"MARCH 2025","votes":"0","username":"ALP GLOBAL","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"It is baby friendly or not ?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"PM","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date??","answer":"MARCH 2025","votes":"0","username":"ALP GLOBAL","date":"2022-05-24 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it dusting powder?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"Mona Lisa","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"},{"question":"Can be used for 3 year old child?","answer":"YES","votes":"0","username":"ALP GLOBAL","date":"2022-05-18 00:00:00"},{"question":"Manufacturing date?","answer":"1/1/2022","votes":"0","username":"Gurvinder singh","date":"2022-04-25 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the manufacturing and expire date of this product","answer":"Buy it to know","votes":"0","username":"AvidBuyer","date":"2022-05-06 00:00:00"},{"question":"Expiry date?","answer":"Check on tin","votes":"0","username":"Mona Lisa","date":"2022-05-04 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35c4ff124495add20265"},"product_asin":"B00I4S88K4","QAs":[{"question":"Can we apply it on face?","answer":"Not advisable as it is prickly heat powder.","votes":"0","username":"Ravi Kiran","date":"2021-11-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Does this still come with free 50g nycil powder?","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"LookRavish","date":"2021-04-05 00:00:00"},{"question":"With it free product have ??","answer":"Yes","votes":"0","username":"LookRavish","date":"2020-07-03 00:00:00"}]}
{"_id":{"$oid":"636a35c4ff124495add20269"},"product_asin":"B077H177YP","QAs":[{"question":"Is it 300g or 600 g?","answer":"300 gms and very fragrant.","votes":"0","username":"Renuka Mani","date":"2022-07-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Product name listing it is described that the scent is \"sandal\" but in product details it is mentioned as \"scent: lavender\". which is correct?","answer":"sandal 🪵","votes":"0","username":"Nitish Yadav…","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date of above park avenue sandal talcum powder available in stock at present","answer":"Please don't purchase this item. It is not a talcum powder but a flour. Utter waste.","votes":"0","username":"N.Muthusamy","date":"2022-02-20 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is the expiry date of available stock.  you hv mentioned dec-2021 , how we can accept??","answer":"expired date of product is 3 year","votes":"0","username":"Nitish Yadav…","date":"2022-06-02 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is it one plus one ?","answer":"Yes, it was 1+1 when I bought this talcum powder.","votes":"0","username":"Quality Analyst","date":"2020-06-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"Is this a Park Avenue Branded product??","answer":"Not even near to Park Avenue brand. Do not go thru the description. Container doesn't have the name of Park Avenue, nor feont or back n not even marketed by Park Avenue. It is some local brand, you can use it, but fragrance lasts a day or less.","votes":"0","username":"Abdul Subhan","date":"2020-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"This is face powder","answer":"It's a body talc not face powder.","votes":"0","username":"Anirudha Das","date":"2019-10-28 00:00:00"},{"question":"What is actual MRP on bottle","answer":"165 per box","votes":"0","username":"Abdul Subhan","date":"2020-05-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"this is long lasting product?","answer":"Fregrance is awesome but not long lasting","votes":"0","username":"Khushi Verma","date":"2019-09-22 00:00:00"},{"question":"Total quantity in one bottle","answer":"Ii contains 300 gm in each can. So total 600 gms for the stated price..... value for money.","votes":"0","username":"Rocky kumar ahluvalia","date":"2019-09-17 00:00:00"}]}
